(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
The Rise of the Nut Warrior
In a kingdom far far away
Where all nyut-nyut lives,
A sudden calamity strikes
among the nyut-nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere
and created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left hopeless
until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived
to find a legendary weapon,
the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel
will bring an end to this calamity...
強くなれる理由を知った
I have learned the reason to be strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward
紅蓮華
Lyrics: LiSA  Music: 草野華余子
Gurenge
Lyrics: LiSA  Music: Kayoko Kusano
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Intoxicated by a mud-stained revolving lantern
こわばる心
My heart stiffens
震える手は掴みたいものがある
There's something my trembling hands want to grasp
それだけさ
That's all it is
夜の匂いに
In the scent of the night
(I'll spend all thirty nights)
空睨んでも
Even if I glare at the sky
(Staring into the sky)
変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ
The only thing I can change is myself
それだけさ
That's all it is
強くなれる理由を知った　僕を連れて進め
I know why I can be strong, take me with you and move forward
どうしたって！
No matter what happens!
消せない夢も
The dreams I can't erase
止まれない今も
The present I can't stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone's sake
ありがとう　悲しみよ
Then thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of defeat
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ！
Crimson lotus flower, bloom in full glory!
運命を照らして
Illuminate our destiny
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning pierces my ears
戸惑う心
My bewildered heart
優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある
Kindness alone isn't enough to protect what matters
わかってるけど
I know that, but still...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil tangled beneath the surface
透けて見える偽善に天罰
Divine punishment for transparent hypocrisy
(Tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me why)
I don't need you!
逸材の花より
Rather than a flower of rare talent
挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
The single bloom that persists through challenge is beautiful
乱暴に敷き詰められた
The path roughly paved
トゲだらけの道も
With thorns and briars
本気の僕だけに現れるから
Will reveal its true form only to the serious me
乗り越えてみせるよ
I'll show you I can overcome it
簡単に片付けられた
Dismissed so easily
守れなかった夢も
The dreams I couldn't protect
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
Will take root in my crimson heart
この血に宿って
And dwell within this blood
ヒト知れずはかない
Fleeting, unknown to others
散りゆく結末
The scattering end
無情に破れた
Cruelly torn asunder
悲鳴の風吹く
The wind of screams blows
誰かの笑う影
The shadow of someone's laughter
誰かの泣き声
The sound of someone's weeping
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness
どうしたって！
No matter what happens!
消せない夢も
The dreams I can't erase
止まれない今も
The present I can't stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone's sake
ありがとう　悲しみよ
Then thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of defeat
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ！
Crimson lotus flower, bloom in full glory!
運命を照らして
Illuminate our destiny
Oh no!
Everything is burned down.
My house and the entire village is destroyed.
What is going on?
Are you alright?
A giant monster...
...burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad.
Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry.
I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that, I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager.
Oh, I will.
ライオン
Lyrics: Gabriela Robin  Music: Gabriela Robin
Lion
星を廻せ　世界のまんなかで
Spin the stars, in the middle of the world
くしゃみすればどこかの森で蝶が乱舞
If I sneeze, butterflies will dance in some forest
君が守るドアのかぎで　ただ目覚める
I simply wake up with the key to the door you protect
はずかしいほど　かたすみで
Strong is the lion licking its wounds
なめ合ってるライオンはつよい
In a corner so shameful
生き残りたい　生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
I still want to stay alive
星座の導きで　いま、見つめ合った
Guided by the constellations, our eyes met just now
生き残りたい　途方に暮れて
I want to survive, at my wit's end
キラリ枯れてゆく
Sparkling and withering away
本気のカラダ　見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self
私、眠らない
I will not sleep
風はやがて　東へ向かうだろう
The wind will eventually head east
高気圧のこの星の今日を　覆うそう
And likely cover today on this high-pressure planet
誘い水　飲んだ胸がつらい
My chest hurts from drinking the decoy water
遠巻きな物語　かじり合う
Distant stories, gnawing at each other
骨の髄まで
To the marrow of our bones
生き残りたい　生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
I still want to stay alive
星座の導きで　いま、見つめ合った
Guided by the constellations, our eyes met just now
生き残りたい　途方に暮れて
I want to survive, at my wit's end
キラリ枯れてゆく
Sparkling and withering away
本気のカラダ　見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self
私、眠らない
I will not sleep
何しに生まれたの？
What were we born for?
何しにここにいる？
What are we doing here?
生き残りたい　埋まらない傷
I want to survive, I was afraid of the light
光　恐れてた
On my unhealable wounds
許された命が　いま、惹かれ合った
Pardoned lives have now been drawn together
さまよい果てて　君のとなりで　火照り　沈めて
At my wandering's end, I calm my flush by your side
本気のカラダ　見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self
私、眠らない
I will not sleep
生き残りたい　崖っぷちでいい
I want to survive, even on a cliff's edge
君を愛してる
I love you
目覚めた本能が　いま、惹かれ合った
Awakened instincts have now been drawn together
狂気に変えて　祈り捧ぐよ
Turning it into madness, I offer my prayers
君を愛してる
I love you
星座の導きで...
Guided by the constellations...
生き残りたい　まだ生きたいよ
I want to survive, I still want to live
君を愛してる
I love you
本気の心　見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true heart
私、眠らない
I will not sleep
星が降る
Stars Fall
Lyrics: 秘那間トウカ (ヒナマトウカ)
Music, Arrangement: JunbugP
Lyrics: Hinama Touka
ハネもない この私が
With no wings, even I...
憧れてた あの空
...longed for that sky
背伸びして 星を掴む
Stretching upwards to grab the stars
真似をしてみた
I tried to reach for them
負けないで 願いさえも
Don't give up, even if the darkness
飲み込む闇 それでも
Swallows your very wishes
手探りで 夢のカケラ
Let's go and gather the fragments of our dreams
集めに行こうよ
Searching through the dark
ただグルグル 回る 車輪の中で
Inside a wheel that just spins round and round
走っても 走っても たどり着けなくて
No matter how much I run, I never arrive
先を 行く君の 背中ばかりを 見ていた
I was only looking at your back as you went ahead
いつか 超えられる
I want to become stronger
もっと強くなりたい
So I can surpass you one day
たったひとり 生まれてきた
Even if you lose the memory
その記憶も なくして
Of being born all alone
泣き声も 届かないと 嘆いてみても
Even if you grieve that your cries won't reach
信じていて 大きな木に しがみついた 爪痕
Believe in the claw marks left on the big tree
あの空へ 近づこうと している証
They are the proof you're trying to reach that sky
風が 雲を流して
The wind blows the clouds away
星が降る
The stars fall
ハネもない この私が
With no wings, even I...
憧れてた あの空
...longed for that sky
背伸びして 星を掴む
Stretching upwards to grab the stars
真似をしてみた
I tried to reach for them
負けないで 願いさえも
Don't give up, even if the darkness
飲み込む闇 それでも
Swallows your very wishes
手探りで 夢のカケラ
Let's go and gather the fragments of our dreams
集めに行こうよ
Searching through the dark
Ugh... I think after all this singing...
...my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster!
Ho ho ho!
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
As I,
the Keeper of the legendary weapon Nut Blade
will lend you its power.
Is this
the voice of the Fireblade Priestess?
Yes, you are right.
I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade
if you can prove yourself
that you have the spirit to fight the pink giant monster.
Hah, okay!
Dragon Screamer
Dragon Wall!
胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
Carve it in your heart, the leader of the era
見た目より かわったかなりこれば
It’s changed more than it looks
乾いた心 荒むよりは
Rather than a dry heart growing desolate
時に泣いてみれば 見えてくる
If you try to cry sometimes, you'll see
明日駆けるのは 紛れもなく 新しい自分
The one running toward tomorrow is surely a new you
誰かのためでもなく ただもっと 上を目指せ
Not for anyone else, just aim higher
Dragon Screamer Why do I, Why do I
昇龍 揚羽だ Why do I, Why do I
Ascending dragon, rising wings, Why do I, Why do I
銀の光が 呼んだ未来が
The future called by the silver light
導きだした 僕らを
Has guided us out
Dragon Screamer Dragon Fever No Question
Dragon Wall!
見えているのに 遥かなゴールは
Even though it's visible, the distant goal
見た目より かなりにハード
Is much harder than it looks
君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
If you have the courage to take a step
やがて開く道が 目指すべき
The path that eventually opens will be your target
場所選ぶのは 紛れもなく 新しい自分
The one choosing the place is surely a new you
翼を手にした君は どの山をも越える
You, having gained wings, will cross any mountain
Dragon Screamer
叫ぶ龍のような
Like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow it all away
迷いとか 恐れを
All the hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer Dragon Fever No Question
Oh my way! Keep the space! 突き抜けていく光 浴びて行くぜ
On my way! Keep the space! I'm basking in the light breaking through
In the case! 気持ちハイペース! テステス! 走り去った様に見える
In the case! High-paced feeling! Test test! Looks like I’ve run away
上目指す! 諦めず 探し続ける 時代のリーダー
Aim high! Without giving up, keep searching for the leader of the era
いつまでも変わらぬ夢 ベクトル! 空に浮かぶドラゴン
An unchanging dream forever, a vector! The dragon floating in the sky
誰かが見たはず!
Someone must have seen it!
明日の世界は空の手に!
Tomorrow's world is in the sky's hands!
Dragon Screamer
昇龍 揚羽だ Why do I, Why do I
Ascending dragon, rising wings, Why do I, Why do I
銀の光が 呼んだ未来が
The future called by the silver light
導きだした 僕らを
Has guided us out
Dragon Screamer Dragon Fever
No Question
Dragon Screamer 叫ぶ龍のような
Dragon Screamer, like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow it all away
迷いとか 恐れを
All the hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer Dragon Fever
No Question
You have proven me your spirit.
I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you!
I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster!
Now I have the Nut Blade,
I shall continue my journey to defeat the giant pink monster.
If my hunch was right, I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, O Mighty Dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた。
I was defeated by the pink giant beast.
今は力が入らん...
Now I have no strength...
巣も破壊されてしまった。
My nest was also destroyed.
Oh no, that is bad!
I can help you recover if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange!
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
おおかみは赤ずきんに恋をした
The Wolf Fell in Love with Little Red Riding Hood
偶然から始まる
Starting from a chance encounter
必然のワンシーン
a scene of necessity
遠くに見えたのは
Visible in the distance
揺れる赤い色
was a swaying red color
不思議な森の奥で
In the depths of a mysterious forest
見つけた黒いカゲと
a black shadow found
何かが始まる予感
A premonition that something is starting
怖くて逃げ出した
I ran away in fear
「出会い」は
The "encounter" is
終着の
the end of
シナリオ
the scenario
だからわざと遠回りをした
so I intentionally took a detour
会いたいなんて
To want to meet you
触れたいなんて
To want to touch you
話したいなんて
To want to talk to you
思わない
I don't think about it
かよわい君と
The frail you
鋭い僕が出会う
and the sharp me meet
それが「終わり」さ
That's the "end"
残酷だって
Even if it's cruel
罵ったって
Even if you revile it
運命は変わらない
Fate doesn't change
ああ　どうして君が
Ah, why are you
どうして僕が
Why am I
おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
the wolf and Little Red Riding Hood?
きっと君は今日も
Surely you will again today
この道を訪れる
visit this path
そして僕は今日もずっと
And I will again today, forever
見守るしかできない
do nothing but watch over you
君はあの木の先で
You're beyond that tree
いつも通り隠れてる
hiding as usual
私は気づかぬフリしたまま
I, while pretending not to notice
通り過ぎた
passed by
視線は
The gaze is
交わらぬ
not crossing
声は届かない
The voice won't reach
ため息だけが虚しく重なる
Only sighs vainly pile up
会えなくたって
Even if we can't meet
触れなくたって
Even if we can't touch
話せなくたって
Even if we can't talk
いいから
it's fine
頼りない君と　ぎこちない僕が
the helpless you and the awkward me
そこにいるだけでいいんだ
just being there is enough
これが「恋」だって
If I don't say
言わないなら
this is "love"
言葉なんてなくていい
then there's no need for words
ああ　考えたって
Ah, even if I think
考えたって
Even if I think about it
エンディングは変わらない
the ending won't change
会いたかったんだ
I wanted to meet you
触れたかったんだ
I wanted to touch you
話したかった
I wanted to talk
本当は
Truly
かわいい君と　優しい僕が
the cute you and the kind me
出会い結ばれるエンド
meet and have a happy end
何回だって
Any number of times
神様に願ったよ
I prayed to God
でも　悲しいくらい
But it's so sad
悲しいくらい
So sad
おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
we're the wolf and Little Red Riding Hood
泣いてる君を　慰めたくて　伸ばした腕が震える
My outstretched arm trembles, wanting to comfort the crying you
愛しているよ　抱きしめたいよ　だけどできないんだよ
I love you, I want to hold you, but I can't
どうあがいたって
No matter how much I struggle
どう願ったって
No matter how much I pray
爪も牙も消えない
my claws and fangs won't disappear
だから　ただ待ってるよ
So I'll just wait
君の涙が
until your tears
止むまであの木の先で
stop, beyond that tree
ずっと
Forever
Ah, here we go!
If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する。
I'm grateful.
よし、完全回復だ。
Good, full recovery.
今すぐ怪獣の元へ案内しよう。
I shall guide you to the monster right away.
Okay, let's go!
FLY HIGH!!
飛べ　FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼で
With shining wings
今
now
全部全部を
everything, everything
蹴散らして 飛べ
kick it all away and fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future
傷だらけの若鳥が
A young bird covered in wounds
空を睨んでる
is glaring at the sky
低空飛行する奴らが
Those who fly at low altitudes
笑おうと
may laugh at you
海の果てが見たい
but I want to see the end of the sea
心を無にして
Emptying your heart
向かい風に乗り
riding the headwind
助走をつけて
gaining momentum
HOP, STEP, JUMPで
with a hop, step, and jump
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼が
the shining wings
君をどこへだって
will take you anywhere
連れて行く
anywhere you want to go
青い衝動と
With blue impulse
本能と
instinct
爪牙を剥き出しにして
and baring your claws and fangs
艱難の旅路も
Even on a difficult journey
夢叶うまで
until your dream comes true
何度だって
no matter how many times
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future
ぽつり降り出した雨が
The rain that started falling
翼 震わせる
makes your wings tremble
行く手には黒い雲
Black clouds lie ahead
今長い
now a long
嵐の夜が来る
stormy night is coming
轟く雷鳴と
With roaring thunder
砕ける波濤を
and crashing waves
飾りに（して）
as your ornaments
アンストッパブルで
being unstoppable
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
いつも胸の奥を
The flames that always
焦がす焔が
burn deep in your chest
道を照らし出す
light up the way
どデカい夜明け前の咆哮が
The huge roar before dawn
才能の花 咲かすから
will make the flowers of talent bloom
命 尽きるまで
Until the end of your life
限界を超え
surpassing your limits
最速で
at maximum speed
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
Ah...
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼が
the shining wings
君をどこへだって
will take you anywhere
連れて行く
anywhere you want to go
青い衝動と
With blue impulse
本能と
instinct
爪牙を剥き出しにして
and baring your claws and fangs
全部
everything
全部を
蹴散らして
kick it all away
飛べ
and Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
いつも胸の奥を
The flames that always
焦がす焔が
burn deep in your chest
道を照らし出す
light up the way
どデカい夜明け前の
The huge roar before dawn
咆哮が
the roar
才能の花 咲かすから
will make the flowers of talent bloom
命 尽きるまで
Until the end of your life
限界を超え
surpassing your limits
最速で
at maximum speed
飛べ
Fly
FLY!
HIGH!!
最果ての未来へ
To the furthest future
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you, would you love...
MIR//or
Lyrics: Ayunda Risu Music, Arrangement: フェリギア (Feryquitous)
Well, I love you like you love me too,
utaraku kecil dahulu.
my childhood north.
The love will last,
it will...
...selamanya kukan peduli.
...forever I will care.
Right to me,
broken thing have I become.
And you see life is better.
Truly,
I've never had enough.
Ordinary day,
it seems the clouds of life in the sky
painted color in my paradise.
Berisik hujan,
The noisy rain,
menghapuskan segala luka duka emosi manusia.
wiping away all wounds, sorrows, and human emotions.
Siap melepaskan
Ready to release
berkobar-kobar selamanya.
burning forever.
Well, I love you like you love me too,
utaramu lebih dahulu.
your north came before.
The love will last,
it will...
...selamanya kukan ada di sini.
...forever I will be here.
To me,
enchanting have I become.
And you see life is better.
Truly,
I will never have enough.
Ordinary day,
it seems the clouds of life in the sky
painted color in my paradise.
Berisik hujan,
The noisy rain,
menghapuskan segala luka duka emosi manusia.
wiping away all wounds, sorrows, and human emotions.
Rapuh dan terjatuh,
Fragile and fallen,
melayang di dunia.
floating in the world.
The horror lingers on my ego.
Winding light that radiates
evaporates the setting sun.
As long as whisper follow me,
don't never let go.
Bahagia,
Happiness,
harap yang jadi nyata,
a hope that becomes real,
hanya merdu.
only melodious.
To me,
obsessive have I become.
And you see life is better.
Truly,
I will never give enough.
Ordinary,
I will be the clouds and the
color of rainbow start to show in my paradise.
Berisik hujan,
The noisy rain,
menghapuskan segala luka duka emosi manusia.
wiping away all wounds, sorrows, and human emotions.
Rapuh dan terlena,
Fragile and captivated,
melayang di dunia.
floating in the world.
I finally...
...nice to meet you,
awan gelap yang kusebut utaraku.
the dark clouds that I call my north.
Berisik hujan membasuh bersih
The noisy rain washes clean
suka dan duka perasaan
the joys and sorrows of feelings
dan melebur
and merges
satu warna yang bermakna.
into one meaningful color.
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut-Nuts from misery!
Whoa! I can't believe that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute. Aw!
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら放つ月
Fluttering, the moon gives off its light
夜明けが見たいって
Saying that I want to see the dawn
叫んだ空
The sky I shouted to
ヒバリ
Hibari (Skylark)
神様気取りのままのトモダチが
A friend who's still acting like a god
世界を愛して壊しちゃいました
Loved the world and ended up breaking it
誰のもの 誰のもの 私のもの
Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine
邪魔者は排除した
I've eliminated all obstacles
カントがなんとか言ってたって
Even if Kant said something about it
エゴに捕まって拒めないんだ
I'm caught in my ego and can't refuse
まだ足りない もの足りない 死にたくない
It's not enough, something's missing, I don't want to die
機械仕掛けの狂った声で
With a clockwork, crazed voice
大人達が言う「もう、いいよ」
The adults say, "That's enough already"
「うんざりだよ」「死んどろーも」
"I'm fed up," "Death syndrome"
「愛してるわ」
"I love you"
「もうやめてよ」
"Stop it already"
心でモノを量ってきた
I've been weighing things with my heart
売れば幸せですか？
Will I be happy if I sell it?
作られたショーケース 抜け出したい基盤
A fabricated showcase, a base I want to escape
世界 移ろいの果て
At the end of the world's transitions
魂をいったいどこに隠した？
Just where did you hide your soul?
甘やかな香が宵分に
A sweet scent in the night divide
天つ音め 歌と舞う
Celestial sound maiden, dance with the song
ヒバリの空
The skylark's sky
輪廻転生 機械論 進化論
Reincarnation, Mechanism, Evolution
人が人でなくなってゆく
Humans are ceasing to be human
血に形り焼べ色取れ
Formed in blood, burned and colored
泡沫を未来へ届けるよ
I'll deliver the bubbles to the future
空から空へと繋げるよ
Connecting sky to sky
限りなく泣くひばり達を遺す
Leaving behind the skylarks that cry without end
何て本を聞かせてくれたっけ？
What kind of book did you read to me again?
メリディアの二人のこと
The story of the two in Meridia
愛してる 嘘でもいいから一度だけでも
I love you; even if it's a lie, just once
聞かせてよ
Let me hear it
どこかで どこで笑ってました？
Somewhere, just where were you laughing?
今は幸せですか？
Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま 届かない想い
Left behind, feelings that won't reach
「ごめんね」 「何で言えなかったかな」
"I'm sorry," "Why couldn't I say it?"
悲しい思い出は風に隠した
I hid the sad memories in the wind
歌よ あなたのもとへ
O song, go to you
天つ音め 時を舞う
Celestial sound maiden, dance through time
ヒバリの空
The skylark's sky
独りでも笑っていけるんだ
I can keep smiling even if I'm alone
独りでは生きてゆけないんだ
I can't live on my own
ずっと拒んだり 愛したり
Constantly refusing, constantly loving
裏で殺されたりすれば生きていけるよ
If I'm killed behind the scenes, then I can live
心でモノを量ってきた
I've been weighing things with my heart
売れば幸せですか？
Will I be happy if I sell it?
作られたショーケース
A fabricated showcase
もう逃げ出さない不可避未来
An inevitable future I'll no longer escape
月先の鍵
The key beyond the moon
魂をいったいどこに隠した？
Just where did you hide your soul?
甘やかな香が宵分に
A sweet scent in the night divide
天つ音め 歌と舞う
Celestial sound maiden, dance with the song
夜明けを告げたら
If the dawn is announced
ヒバリの空
The skylark's sky
Hi everyone!
Woo!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance?
Do you like it?
Did you guys have fun?
And also for celebrating my victory
and my birthday...
...we have special merch!
Yes! So here's the merch!
Ayunda Risu Birthday 2026
Woo!
Whoa! How cool is it?
And it's not only cool...
this year's merch was designed to be useful too.
誕生日記念 2026
Birthday Commemoration 2026
So let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
A3 Tapestry
Ooh! Whoa! Haha!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry
drawn by natural-sensei!
Whoa, the whole illustration just... whoa.
It looks super awesome,
it looks so cool!
You can see that I'm holding my beloved...
Just look at that Warrior Risu
with full dark side.
Isn't it awesome? Woo!
Don't miss it!
And also don't forget,
you guys gotta buy it at least five, okay?
And I think
let's see what we have next.
Tumbler
Woo! A super cute tumbler for everybody.
So you guys won't forget to hydrate.
You can use it to drink water
and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it every day, okay?
And next we have this.
Squirrel Smartphone Ring
Whoa, a smartphone ring!
Ooh!
So you can be super comfortable
and remember me when you're holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very, very convenient.
And I think
let's see the full set now!
Woo! Whoa! There's so much stuff actually.
And also don't forget we have the
full set purchase bonus here!
Set Purchase Bonus
So I will explain it a little bit.
For those of you who purchase the full set
will also receive a signed foil-stamped postcard.
And for my Super Risu-naru
who purchase the limited edition full set
will receive a postcard autographed
by none other than me!
Autographed by me!
Isn't it awesome? Whoa!
And the preorder window is only a month.
So make sure that you don't miss it.
Oh, oh, oh, also one more thing!
Did you guys listen to my new original song
"Hoshigafuru"?
It will be officially released after this stream
at midnight JST.
JST, okay? On my YouTube channel.
So go listen to it and,
maybe who knows that later we will have MV for it?
I don't know!
And last but not least,
for all of you who joined my membership...
...you don't want to miss a special additional
3D performance in membership
just right after this show has ended.
If you haven't joined my membership yet,
do not hesitate
because the extra show is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for?
Join membership now! Woo!
Woo! Ho ho ho! Oops.
Um, but I think the time is up.
And I have to continue, but yes,
I have to continue with the membership show now.
So thank you so much everyone for your support
for this whole six years especially.
And thank you for celebrating my birthday
together with me.
So, poroporo atsu-risu!
Thumbnail Illustrator: local catto
3D Animation: OCTOLOID
Sound effects
Planning: Ayunda Risu
Cinematography: カバー株式会社
Cinematography: COVER Corp.
General Direction: Ayunda Risu / カバー株式会社
General Direction: Ayunda Risu / COVER Corp.
Produced by: Ayunda Risu
Written and Directed by: Ayunda Risu
The Rise of the Nut Warrior